postable.com 2019-04-07

# Privacy Policy | Postable

Postable is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes the information we collect through our Site, how we use it, and how you can make choices about use of that information. By using our Site you agree to this Privacy Policy. 

We strive to treat our users the way we want to be treated online. In short, we do the following. 

(1) We collect information to facilitate the basic functionality of, and to improve, our Site.

(2) We share information (a) as you direct us; (b) with service providers (such as our hosting and email providers), like many websites you use daily; and (c) to protect our users, artists, and ourselves from general bad-doing (such as illegal activities). 

Please read on for details about how we collect and use information, and your privacy. 

### Collection of Information

When you register for an Account and submit information for a user’s Address Book or otherwise on our Site, we collect personally identifiable information about you ("Personal Information"), which may include such information as your name, physical address, zip code, telephone number(s), e-mail address(es), birth month and day, marital status, name of spouse. If you provide information about anyone other than yourself, you represent and warrant that you have the permission and right to provide the information. If you submit your information in response to a registered user's invitation, your Personal Information will not be shared with any third parties for marketing purposes. If you register for an Account, your Personal Information will be used to maintain your Account and Address Book, and we may also send you emails from time to time with information about new features or other news that we think will be of interest to you. If you no longer wish to receive this information from us, you can follow the “unsubscribe” instructions in the messages or you can opt out by contacting us at [info@postable.com](mailto:info@postable.com).

To help us improve our services, we may also collect information to analyze how visitors use our Site, including the time and date of visits to our Site, the referring website, the length of the visit to our Site, the web pages viewed during a visit, time spent on a particular web page, the links followed, the type of web browser used, the web site visited before and after our Site, and the visitor’s IP address (which is the number assigned to the visitor’s computer to identify its location on the Internet). While we do not use this information to identify visitors individually, we reserve the right to do so in circumstances where we determine in our reasonable judgment it may be appropriate to comply with legal process or law enforcement or to protect our rights or the rights of any third party.

### Cookies

Our Site uses cookies, which are small data files placed on your computer. For example, cookies keep track of whether you are logged in to your Account. You are not required to accept cookies from our Site. You can disable or delete the cookies, by using your web browser's options.

### Protection and Sharing of Information

We will share your Personal Information only with the registered user to whom you submitted it for use in his or her Address Book and with service providers who help us operate our Site (such as hosting and email service providers). We reserve the right to disclose and use Personal Information and other information collected on our Site in special circumstances (including to enforce this Privacy Policy or any other part of our Terms, to comply with legal process, law enforcement, or law, to protect our property or rights or the rights or safety of any third party, to address suspected illegal activity, and for similar reasons we determine in good faith are appropriate). If we enter into a business transition, such as a merger, consolidation, acquisition, or sale of all or part of our assets that includes our Site, your Personal Information will likely be transferred along with our other assets.  

### Review and Update Your Personal Information

If you have an Account and wish to review and update your Personal Information, you can do so through your Account profile page on our Site. If you want a registered user to update your contact information in his or her Address Book, please contact that person directly.

### Security

We strive to keep your Personal Information in a secure manner and safeguard it from unauthorized access. Of course, no transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, so you provide your Personal Information at your own risk.

### Location of Servers and Transfer of Information

Our servers are located in the United States. If you are located outside of the United States, you understand that the information you provide through our Site will be transferred to the United States. By using our Site or providing your Personal Information to us, you consent to this transfer to and to the collection, storage, processing and use of your Personal Information in the United States in accordance with these Terms. If you are located in the United States, our service providers may not be located in your geographic area in the United States. By providing your Personal Information on our Site, you consent to the transfer of your Personal Information to these service providers. If any applicable law prohibits collection, use, storage, and sharing of your Personal Information in accordance with these Terms, you may not use our Site or provide Personal Information to it.

### Children Under Age 13

Our Site is designed for use solely by individuals 13 years and older. By using our Site, you represent to us that you are at least 13 years old. If you are not at least 13 years old, you may not use our Site. You may not use our Site to request information from anyone under the age of 13 and we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that any personally identifiable information has been collected from a child under the age of 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you are a parent or legal guardian and you believe that your child under age 13 may have provided personally identifiable information through our Site, please contact us at [info@postable.com](mailto:info@postable.com).

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may modify this Privacy Policy from time to time by displaying updated Terms on the Site. Your continued use of the Site after the updated Privacy Policy is displayed indicates your agreement to the modified Privacy Policy.

### Questions

For any questions or comments you may have about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at: [info@postable.com](mailto:info@postable.com).
